name: 'Common Verbs'
questions:
  -
    question: 'I $ my friend, but he didn''t answer his phone so I left a voicemail.'
    answers:
      - texted
      - emailed
      - called
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Can you $ the light please? I try to sleep.'
    answer:
      - 'turn off'
      - 'turn on'
      - 'turn up'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ a letter from my grandpa yesterday. He lives in Germany.'
    answers:
      - sent
      - got
      - get
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '"Please $ me a story!" I asked my dad before I went to bed.'
    answers:
      - say
      - tell
      - speak
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I always $ my keys! Can you open the door please?'
    answers:
      - find
      - seek
      - lose
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I need to $ the house early to get on a train.'
    answers:
      - come
      - arrive
      - leave
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ your umbrella. It might rain.'
    answers:
      - Give
      - Take
      - Leave
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'Is his birthday next week! I need to $ him a present.'
    answers:
      - give
      - take
      - call
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'Did you $ my e-mail yesterday? It has all the details about my party.'
    answers:
      - leave
      - send
      - get
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Can I $ the light? I want to read a book.'
    answers:
      - 'turn off'
      - 'turn on'
      - turn
    correct: 2
